Yun Sheng Ho

UX/UI designer

√ Yunshengho94@gmail.com

() +34657495511

Barcelona

in www.linkedin.com/in/yunsheng-ho/



"Empathy is seeing with the eyes of another, listening with the ears of another and feeling with the heart of another."

- Alfred Adler

UX designer and marketing executive with 2 years experience executing market research plans, conducting surveys and focus groups, analyzing data from sources, including Google Analytics, and increasing engagement via email marketing and social media campaigns.

Experience working in AGILE teams with emphasis on Lean UX, and design thinking at the MVP stage. Always empathetic and experienced in UX research techniques, such as user journeys, interviews, and empathy maps. Adapts 8 points grid (pixel perfect), suitable color composition, and typefaces into interface design. Working knowledge of HTML and CSS.

My marketing background empowers my ability to research users, analyze results and make decisions. As an art amateur, my work allows me to always be creative and opened-mind, no matter the canvas.

Skills









Software

Sketch / Figma /Photoshop /Al

Google Analytics

Presta shop / Wordpress

Facebook Business Manager

Principle / Flinto

HTML/CSS

Soft Skills



– Portfolio:

Behance: www.behance.net/yunshengho **Medium:** medium.com/@yunshengho

Experience

UX UI Designer 2020- NOw Neoland

Marketing & Communication manager 2020- Actual

Brooklyn Café

Marketing & Communication executive 2020-2019

Nevado complements

Marketing & Communication executive 2018-2019

2010-2019

Gaviria Jewellery

Education

Master in Direct Marketing and Interactive Marketing (Digital)

2018-2019

Insa Business school

Master in Fashion Marketing and Communication

2017-2018

Instituto Europeo di Design (IED)

Double Bachelor degrees in Marketing Managment

2016-2017

ESERP Business School